CS-700 Assignment 5

This assignment contains a program take a user input and then a program will run to read a file and create a binary tree which stores alphabets in the nodes in a specific order. Then we map the alphabets with their respective morse code and store it a map. Then the user input is encoded into morse code and then decoded into message again.

1. Main file containing both modules.
	a. Summary - . Running the main() function will run the program and ask for user input which will then be encoded to morse code and decoded back to message.
	b. It contains the following file :
		i. main.cpp

2. Morse Code Encoder/Decoder -
	a. Summary - Running this program will read a file then create a binary tree and then encode the user message to morse code and then decode the morse code into message.
	b. It contains the following files :
		i. MorseCode.cpp - contains all the implementations of member functions of the class MorseCode.
		ii. MorseCode.h - contains functions prototypes of class MorseCode
		iii. Binary_Tree.h - contains functions for a Binary tree
		iv. BTNode.h - contains functions for a binary tree node

Github Repo Link -> https://github.com/syedfaisaljaved/cs700assignment5
